Thank you, sir.
Terima kasih, Pak.
Uncle.
Paman.
There's another problem.
Ada masalah lagi.
Mm.
Hmm.
The spirit power is too weak.
Kekuatan spiritualku terlalu lemah.
Still nowhere near
Masih jauh kalah
what we had at the Meng family
dengan yang dulu di keluarga Meng.
when we found those spirit stones.
Batu spiritual yang ditemukan dulu benar-benar berguna.
Daolang said before
Dulu Daolang bilang
it was the two young ladies from Jia and Tang
dua nona dari keluarga Jia dan Tang
who saved Meng Yan.
menyelamatkan Meng Yan.
The younger generation of Tang and Jia
Anak-anak muda keluarga Tang dan Jia
used to be two-faced,
dulu memang kelihatan munafik,
but at least they called me uncle.
tapi setidaknya masih memanggilku paman.
We all kept up appearances.
Semua masih menjaga muka.
But this time,
Tapi kali ini,
they openly stand against me.
mereka terang-terangan melawan aku.
Something strange is definitely going on.
Ada yang aneh, pasti ada masalah.
There's Jia Yuer,
Ada Jia Yuer,
and Tang Yuyan.
dan Tang Yuyan.
Only that old lady from the Tang family
Hanya nenek dari keluarga Tang
do we still fear a little.
yang masih kami segani.
As for the Jia family,
Sedangkan keluarga Jia,
after the old man died,
setelah kakek itu meninggal,
only Jia Yaozu is left.
tinggal Jia Yaozu saja.
He's just a useless playboy.
Dia cuma pemabuk tak berguna.
His niece
Keponakannya
even dares to mess up our plans.
berani juga mengacaukan urusan kita.
I heard Jia Yuer
Kudengar Jia Yuer
started some Azure Dragon Gang.
mendirikan Geng Naga Hijau.
They keep coming after us.
Terus saja mengejar kita.
Uncle, you must be joking.
Paman, Anda bercanda.
That Azure Dragon Gang
Geng Naga Hijau itu
to us
bagi kita
is just child's play.
cuma mainan anak-anak.
Why are you here?
Ngapain kamu ke sini?
It's been six years.
Enam tahun tak bertemu.
I have so much to tell you.
Banyak yang ingin kukatakan padamu.
No.
Bukan.
Whatever it is, let's talk tomorrow.
Kalau ada yang mau dibicarakan, besok saja.
It's so late now.
Sekarang sudah larut malam.
Do you know
Tahukah kamu
some things can only be said at night?
beberapa hal hanya bisa dibicarakan malam hari?
Don't.
Jangan.
Put on some clothes.
Pakai baju, dong.
It's so cold.
Dingin begini.
If you think I'm cold,
Kalau kau pikir aku kedinginan,
then come closer to me.
mendekatlah padaku.
Don't you like it?
Tidak suka?
I...
Aku...
Stop messing around.
Jangan bercanda.
This is Jia Yuer's house.
Ini rumah Jia Yuer.
What,
Kenapa?
am I not enough alone?
Aku saja tidak cukup?
You want her to join us?
Mau dia ikut bersama kita?
What are you talking about?
Apa maksudmu?
Come out, hurry.
Cepat keluar!
He's such a flirt.
Dia memang genit.
Yuer.
Yuer.
You...
Kamu...
Meng Yan, you're so naughty.
Meng Yan, kamu nakal sekali.
How do you know some things
Bagaimana kau tahu
are more fun with three people
tiga orang melakukannya
than with just two?
lebih seru daripada berdua?
You...
Kamu...
There's still a long time till dawn.
Masih lama sampai pagi.
Shh.
Ssst.
Yuer, your hand...
Yuer, tanganmu...
Wait, that's not right.
Ada yang salah.
Who are you really?
Siapa kalian sebenarnya?
What are you?
Kalian makhluk apa?
Why doesn't my power
Kenapa kekuatanku
work on you?
tak mempan pada kalian?
What we are doesn't matter.
Siapa kami tak penting.
What matters is what you saw.
Yang penting, apa yang kau lihat.
What do you want?
Apa sebenarnya tujuan kalian?
You'll know soon.
Sebentar lagi kau akan tahu.
Meng Yan, get down!
Meng Yan, tiarap!
You...
Kalian...
Are you okay?
Kamu tidak apa-apa?
Wait.
Tunggu sebentar.
That dead toad
Kodok mati itu
how did it show up here?
kenapa datang ke sini?
Dead toad?
Kodok mati?
Mm.
Hmm.
Yuer means the Puppetmaster Toad.
Yuer maksudnya Kodok Dalang.
He's now the most powerful
Sekarang dia di Dai
puppetmancer in Dai.
jadi dalang boneka terkuat.
Two years ago, he single-handedly
Dua tahun lalu, sendirian
wiped out Dai's biggest gang.
menghabisi geng terbesar di Dai.
He became famous overnight.
Langsung jadi terkenal.
They say his puppetmancy is ever-changing.
Katanya Seni Kendali Bonekanya sangat beragam.
No one can tell what's real or fake.
Orang lain tak bisa bedakan mana nyata mana ilusi.
Rumor has it
Ada kabar
he's always coveted
dia selama ini
the Jade Vein of the three great families in Myanmar.
menginginkan Tambang Giok tiga keluarga besar Myanmar.
Puppetmaster Toad.
Kodok Dalang.
That dead toad is always mysterious.
Kodok mati itu memang misterius.
But now it's fine.
Tapi sekarang sudah jelas.
At least we know he's straight.
Setidaknya dia pria tulen.
How do you know?
Kok kamu tahu?
Look at those stockings.
Lihat saja stoking itu.
That's straight guy taste.
Selera pria tulen.
I wouldn't wear them anyway.
Aku sih tak akan pakai.
But I see these puppets
Tapi boneka-boneka ini
don't have any weapons.
tak punya senjata.
They don't seem to want to hurt Meng Yan.
Sepertinya tak ingin melukai Meng Yan.
Oh no.
Sial.
Xiao Duo!
Xiao Duo!
Isn't this your home address?
Bukankah ini alamat rumahmu?
I'm going out for a bit.
Aku keluar sebentar.
Wait here and be good till I return.
Tunggu di sini, jangan ke mana-mana.
Okay?
Oke?
Who are you?
Siapa kamu?
Who am I? And who are you?
Siapa aku, siapa kamu?
All things are different.
Segala sesuatu pasti berbeda.
All things are the same.
Segala sesuatu pasti serupa.
It's you.
Kamu...
Boss Jia, you've had too much.
Bos Jia, Anda mabuk.
We're just getting started.
Baru mulai, belum apa-apa.
You're annoying.
Menyebalkan.
Bottoms up!
Minum habis!
Boss Jia.
Bos Jia.
Drink it all!
Minum semuanya!
Patriarch.
Tuan.
Come.
Ayo.
Let's go, sit over there.
Ayo, duduk di sana.
Patriarch.
Tuan.
Yuyan hasn't come back yet.
Yuyan belum pulang.
Not yet.
Belum.
Someone sent this over.
Ada yang mengirimkan barang ini.
That brat hasn't called all day.
Anak bandel itu seharian tak ada kabar.
She didn't even call home.
Tak tahu telepon ke rumah.
Oh no.
Sial.